tellmemore.com 2008-12-17

# Language Learning software - Auralog. The award-winning method to learn and to speak a foreign language. Learn a language with TeLL me More language software

Auralog Privacy Notice 

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for tellmemorestore.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following: 

1\. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared. 

2\. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data. 

3\. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information. 

4\. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

Information Collection, Use, and Sharing 

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.   
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.   
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. 

**Electronic Newsletters**  
Auralog gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe to Auralog's e-newsletters. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter pointing to the subscription management page.   
**Registration and Order Forms**   
Our site uses registration and order forms for customers who purchase products and services online. We collect a visitor's contact information (such as an email address) and financial information (account or credit card numbers, for example). We use contact information from the registration or order forms to send orders and information about our company to our customers. When necessary, we use customers' contact information to communicate with them. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings as described in the Choice/Opt-Out section below. We use collected financial information to bill the user for requested products and services.   
**Product Information Requests**   
Our site uses several forms for customers to request information. We collect contact information, which we use to send information about our company to our customers. We also use customers' contact information to communicate them when necessary. Visitors may opt-out of receiving future mailings as described in the Choice/Opt-Out section below. 

Your Access to and Control Over Information 

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website: 

  * See what data we have about you, if any. 
  * Change/correct any data we have about you. 
  * Have us delete any data we have about you. 
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**   
Auralog provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us. This site gives users the option to change, modify, or remove their information from our database in order to be assured of not receiving future communications. Auralog learners/customers automatically receive customer news and promotional offers via email to the address they've provided. Notification is provided during the confirmation process, at which time they are also given the opportunity to opt-out of receiving these communications. 

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.   
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. 

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
